{
    "subject": "resource/Colin_Greenwood",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Oxford",
    "human_readable": "Colin Greenwood was born in Oxford.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8726270794868469,
            "question": "Where was Colin Greenwood born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7952426671981812,
            "question": "When was Colin Greenwood born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.628596305847168,
            "question": "Is Colin Greenwood English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6153655648231506,
            "question": "In what city did Colin Greenwood grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5231520533561707,
            "question": "What is Colin Greenwood known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23973529040813446,
            "question": "What is the name of the band that Colin Greenwood is a member of?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23902365565299988,
            "question": "Does Colin Greenwood have any siblings who are also musicians?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16244234144687653,
            "question": "Has Colin Greenwood won any awards for his musical work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13459567725658417,
            "question": "What genre of music is Colin Greenwood's band known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12499982118606567,
            "question": "What musical instrument does Colin Greenwood play?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Colin Greenwood was born in Oxford.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8655_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is Colin Greenwood's band known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8655_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Colin Greenwood won any awards for his musical work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8655_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Colin Greenwood have any siblings who are also musicians?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8655_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8655_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8655_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8655_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8655_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8655_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8655_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8655_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8655_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8655_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8655_63.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Colin Greenwood's birthplace, including:\n\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8655/re-ranker-msmarco/6.txt: \"Colin Greenwood was born in Oxford, England...\"\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8655/re-ranker-msmarco/60.txt: \"He attended Abingdon School in Oxfordshire...\"\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8655/re-ranker-msmarco/43.txt: \"Colin Greenwood was born on June 26, 1969 in Oxford, Oxfordshire, England, UK.\"\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8655/re-ranker-msmarco/17.txt: \"Colin Greenwood was born on 26 June 1969 in Oxford, Oxfordshire, England, UK.\"\n* file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8655/re-ranker-msmarco/37.txt: \"City Oxford\"\n\nAll of these documents confirm that Colin Greenwood was indeed born in Oxford."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Colin Greenwood was born in Oxford, England. This matches the statement \"Colin Greenwood was born in Oxford.\" Therefore, the answer is \"yes\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}